ROSADI

Tehc Enthusiast

Tangerang, Banten 15570 | +62 85717667604 | erosadi.github.io

SUMMARY

I have experience as a managing director for almost two years, in charge of carrying out all activities related to companies such as taxation and banking, besides that I am also responsible for managing the company's website along with the hosting used. Previously I also had experience as a 3D design using the sketchup software to create interior and exterior designs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PT. Bentang Pratama Indonesia

Kota Tangerang, Banten 2020 - 2023

Managing Director

- Manage everything related to the company
- Managing the entire internal system of the company

Extra Work

- WordPress Developer
 - Create and develop a company website using the WordPress CMS
 - Manage the hosting used by the website
 - Redesign the website if there are changes as needed
- IT Helpdesk
 - Help other users in the operation of an application
 - Install software and hardware on the user's computer
 - Overcoming problems or bugs that occur on the user's computer

CV. Garuda Surya Kencana

Kota Tangerang, Banten 2019 - 2020

3D Design

- Make sketches of buildings and rooms within the available land area
- Turn the finished sketch into 3D using the SketchUp software
- Design interior and exterior by adding properties

EDUCATION

Tangerang Muhammadiyah University
Bachelor of Informatics Engineering, GPA 3,16

Kota Tangerang, Banten 2015 - 2019

ORGANIZATION

Head of KKN (Real Work Lecture)
Tangerang Muhammadiyah University

Kota Tangerang, Banten 01/2019 - 02/2019

Member Dicoding Kota Bandung, Jawa Barat Dicoding Course 2020 - Present

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Technical Skills: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Laravel, CMS WordPress, MySQL, Git Version Control, Unified Modelling Laguage, Editing, Design CAD 3D, IT Helpdesk, Microsoft Office

Personal Skills : Problem solving, Self management, Working with people, Technology adaptation